One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Kizaru vs. the Four Captains
Unbelievable!
From his hands, and from his mouth, too?
Scary!
Another one's coming!
Just what the hell is that?!
Like they said, it's a beam!
A beam is just a ray of light!
Having something like that working as a weapon is just a fantasy!
Uh, what are you doing?
Playing dead.
He already knows you're not!
Three Sword Style
Rubber
Diable
Mouton
Mutton
Jet
600 Pound
Cannon
All right!
Did they get him?
They're awesome!
The opponent is a Warlord.
They can't beat him so easily.
I can tell just from their expressions.
Is he really that different?
Does that mean that he's his twin or something?
Yeah, that is a possibility.
Anyway, if he was the real guy, then he would have instantly dodged our attacks.
More importantly, he's not shooting out shock waves, and he doesn't have pads.
But if he's a fake, then that's a problem as well.
That means that there are two people as strong as him.
You hurt me pretty badly...
But don't think that I'm the same as I was earlier!
Karmic Retribution
"Mad Monk" Urouge...
How can a man who was so badly injured until now...
Have gotten this big and strong all of a sudden?
That was Kizaru's laser!
Did you manage to put Kizaru's destructive power into Bartholomew Kuma's body...
Vegapunk?!
Are the Pacifista already this advanced?!
This is getting out of hand!
Yeah, even three men worth over 100 million...
Can't possibly survive when they're up against a Warlord and an admiral!
Rear admiral Drake...
No, former rear admiral...
Didn't you come here to see this?
If you'd like to try fighting, then go ahead.
Seeing how you know the circumstances already...
I guess you're just too terrified to try, right?
But try not to lose your cool, my flimsy little friends.
I'm here too, after all.
Well, I just got to see another interesting thing...
This is the first time I've seen a rare, ancient Zoan-type.
I'm surprised to see that even you have red blood in your veins.
I just saw something really unusual...
I said that I'm here too, didn't I?
One after another...
Seems like all you people worth over 100 million are monsters.
That's pretty scary!
Phase of Demon Subjugation
He vanished!
M-My eyes!
Captain Hawkins!
I can't see!
I don't know what kind of ability you possess, but you have a physical form...
So I suppose you're not a Logia-type.
Captain!
This is bad!
He's exceeded his damage limit!
He's really gonna die!
Here's the first one...
Good work making it this far in your long journey.
Is this music reachin' you?
If you hear me, then tune in!
Navy admiral Kizaru!
He's the "Roaring Tide"...
Everybody, listen to my fighting music!
What?
Here we go!
Check it out!
Well, I doubt a navy admiral would die from something like this, though...
Wow, I sure got to see a lot of interesting stuff.
Well, I'll be getting out of here now.
See ya!
That's awful...
Ooh, what a surprise...
Mirror of Yata
Huh, what?
Hello?
Huh?
Oh, here it is.
Borsalino here.
Old man!
You did have your baby snail-phone with you!
Why didn't you contact me?!
Oh, Sentoumaru-kun!
Don't just say "Oh"!
What're you doing?!
You've arrived on the island, right?!
Well, I couldn't get in touch with you, you see...
I bet you tried to talk into the black snail-phone again, right?!
I told you before, the black snail-phone on your arm is just for tapping!
Oh...
Oh...!
Whatever!
Just hurry up and get back to work!
We've already identified our targets!
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid, and Trafalgar Law, who do you wanna start with?
Oh, is that so?
Then...
Sabaody Archipelago
Grove 12
Zoro!
Hey, Zoro!
Were you really so badly injured that you can't move?
Leave him alone, Luffy!
We've gotta defeat this thing first!
Yeah...
There's no way his wounds from back then could've healed completely...
From what I can see, just standing up to face the enemy must be really painful for him.
If this bastard isn't Bartholomew Kuma, then who is he?!
He looks exactly like one of the Seven Warlords...
What the hell is going on?!
Hey, Zoro!
Split-Hoof
Roseo Blizzard
Chopper!
Strong Hammer
Franky Boxing
Spider Net
We can't take his physical strength lightly either!
Take care!
Here I go!
Swallow
Bond En Avant
H-huh?
I have stopped!
W-Wait, that's dangerous!
Are you planning on killing me?!
...Though I'm already dead...
Wait, this is no time to be saying that...!
Sure Kill Atlas Comet
Now's our chance! Let's run!
That was scary! Thank you so much!
Huh? He's acting strangely...
What? Bombs work on him NOW?
One shot went inside his mouth... Something inside his body must have short-circuited...
His body might be tough, but he's still got blood on the inside.
He's had his entire body modified to become a weapon, just like me...
but he's really a normal human!
Nami-san, watch out! He's found you!
Oh, no!
Ochenta Fleurs
Eighty Flower
Cuatro Manos
Four Hands
Shock!
You did it! He fired off the beam inside his own mouth!
He self-destructed!
Sorry to interrupt your break, mister...
But you should watch out for lightning there!
From dark clouds to the Clima Tact...
Thunder Lance Tempo!
That one definitely worked... Fantastic!
It didn't work at all, did it?! He's still perfectly fine, isn't he?!
Once you get desperate, the fight is over.
Hey, blast him over here!
You're too damn stubborn...
Diable Jambe
Flambage Shot!
Flambé Shot
Alright! He's finally starting to fall apart!
Demonic Spirit
Nine Sword Style
Asura!
W... What is that?!
Zoro multiplied?!
Nine Demonic Flashes
Gear Third!
Let's go!
Go, Luffy!
We just need one more hit!
Rubber
Crush him, Luffy!
Giant Rifle!
I'm shrinking!
We stopped that bastard, right?
We must have...
It almost seems like he's gonna start moving again... Creepy...
If he does, we're doomed.
I'm totally beat, I can't move anymore.
Maybe we should've escaped, instead of trying to fight him?
No, if we can beat him, then that's what we should do.
He'd chase us wherever we went.
But what was with that guy anyway?
He's definitely a modified human...
That means that he was once a human who looked just like Bartholomew Kuma.
I'd guess they were twins, or perhaps they just found someone who looked super similar...
I suppose that's the most likely explanation.
There's no way they could've actually created a human, after all.
PX-4?
Let's rest for a bit...
I never thought we'd be forced to go all-out in a battle so soon...
I want to rest, but we should find a hiding-place first.
If they find us now, we're in big trouble, you know.
I guess that's true.
But...
Wait just a minute, okay?
Man, you guys have really done it now!
What?! Another enemy?!
Where'd that voice come from?!
Up there! They're up there!
Who's there?!
Hey, hey! What a pitiful state you're in, PX-4!
Just building one of you Pacifista costs us as much as an entire warship!
Man, how am I supposed to explain this to that damn Punk?!
Navy Headquarters
Captain of the Science Patrol
Sentoumaru
Another Warlord!
D-Don't tell me that's the real guy?!
Doesn't matter whether he's real or a fake...
We don't have the strength to stand up to that thing again!
He just said "Pacifista"...
"Pacifista"... That's like someone who creates peace, right?
Is that the name of the one we just defeated?
Who are you, broadaxe?!
You don't call a man by his weapon's name!
There's no point in asking me questions.
I have nothing to tell any of you!
I'm the man with the toughest guard in the whole world!
Of course, my mouth is well-guarded too!
Can't you at least tell us your name?!
I have no obligations to answer that!
Didn't I just tell you? I'm the world's most tight-lipped man, Sentoumaru!
Really? Sentoumaru, is it?
I just felt like telling you that!
I wasn't answering your question!
Let's go, PX-1!
He's firing beams from his palms too...
He doesn't have pads.
I didn't want to think about it, but that makes him the third!
What's going on?!
Rather than wondering about that,
it'd be safer for us to run away right now!
If we get into another fight now, someone will definitely die!
Let's run before we meet the admiral...!
Yeah...
Let's run away from here!
We can't stay together... We'll split up and escape!
I think we should run, too!
The three of us should split up!
Sure... Are you gonna be alright?
Shut up!
I'll protect Nami-swan!
Even if it costs me my life!
Right, thank you. Let's get going!
If you're ready to risk your life, then you should be the decoy for all of us!
Ladies only, damn bastard!
Just take care of yourself, panty-man!
Zoro-kun will protect me as well as he can, so don't worry!
Wait a minute, Usopp! I'm hurt...
Do not worry! I shall cover for you!
Your injuries still haven't healed, right?
To tell you the truth, I saw your act of self-sacrifice back on Thriller Bark!
I see...
Thanks!
We're running over there!
Right.
Those beams are scary!
Everyone, we'll meet up at the Sunny in three days!
They're splitting up and running!
Chase them, PX-1!
Don't let them get out of Grove 12, or we'll be in trouble.
Sure Kill Super Smoke Star!
Now's our chance!
You are quite reliable!
Damn! The bridge!
Here he is!
Why did he come here?!
Hey, hey... You...! Hey!
Don't push me!
He went that way? Are they alright?!
You don't have time to worry about others!
I don't have anything against pirates though.
Rubber
Gatling!
What?!
What did he just do?!
You've got some pretty good offensive power, but...
My guard is the strongest in the world!
Leg Locked, Heave-Ho!
Luffy!
What?! He's this strong, too?!
I just thought I'd tell you, I'm not a devil fruit-user!
There's something strange about his techniques...!
W-What?! Who are you?!
You... Get away!
Get away from Zoro, you freak!
Z-Z-Zoro-san!
Zoro-san was hit by a beam!
Hey, Zoro, pull yourself together!
Man, he's late!
So you finally arrived, old man Kizaru?!
Kizaru?!
Be careful! That man is a navy admiral!
Admiral?!
Oh, you're a bit too late...
120 million bounty-head, "Pirate Hunter" Zoro...
I'd heard that you were a reasonably accomplished swordsman...
But seeing how you were beaten with one shot, I suppose you're pretty exhausted, huh?
Damn...
He's an admiral...?
Take yourself a long rest...
Zoro!!!
Hey, he can fire beams too!
This is bad! We've gotta do something!
If he's hit at such a close range, he'll die!
Oh no! Zoro's in trouble!
Usopp!
You... Stop it!
Damn it! Why?!
I can't hit him!
I can't stab him either! What do we do?!
Damn!
You...
Move your leg!
Please move!
That's no use.
I ate the Light Fruit, I'm a light man.
I'm a Logia.
Light man?!
You're kidding, right?! He's gonna die!
Zoro! Run!
Zoro!
My body... won't...
It's no use! That guy is at his limit already!
Veinte Fleur!
Twenty Flower
Alright! Great, Robin!
I won't let you get away.
It's useless.
You'll die now.
So, now you decide to appear...
"Dark King", Rayleigh?
I won't let you take out these youngsters.
Their era is only beginning!
Pops!